All right. How to grow a small account
with the Miami Vice theme colors behind
me and the muscle shirt that makes me
look like I'm from GTA. Right before we
go on a mission and beat up some
bruisers or something, let's break this
down. You got a small account. There's a
couple different things you're going to
want to do differently than with your
large account here. This is my advice.
In theory, let's say you start with like
a hundred bucks. Okay. The first thing
you're going to have to make sure is you
really don't have much draw down to work
with. When I'm trading and I have a
million-doll account here. You can
follow the extremes if you want to see
me trade on a million-doll account. I'm
able to add to the trade a little bit as
I go into a draw down zone. I have a
zone I usually enter in on and I'm
allowed to add a little bit more and
more and more. Basically, with a $100
account, you get one entry. You get have
to use the minimums and you can't really
go into much draw down. So, you have to
be one following the trend. When you're
following the trend, you're going to be
looking for areas that the price comes
back into a zone that you'd be looking
to buy in on a pullback and then wait
for the reaction off of that and then
hopefully use the momentum to catapult
you into larger profits. you're gonna
have to be going for really really all
hail mary bets here, which is the second
major thing is you want to basically
risk the entire account every single
time because if you got a hundred bucks,
you can easily get another 100 bucks
from your next paycheck and you're
trying to snowball that account very
quickly to something that's actually
going to take more time to accumulate
through earnings from your job. And then
number three, and by the way, we're
going to jump into the chart here so I
can show you exactly how you would do
this. Number three, you're going to look
for really low R. And that might be kind
of counterintuitive that you you you
might want to be looking for large R or
really large distance profits because
that way you can snowball that account
like I just said. But what you need to
do is make sure you lock in profits over
and over and over and then use those
profits to then snowball even further.
When you're shooting for lower targets
like sub 2R, you're going to have a much
higher likelihood of you hitting those
trades. You get in, you get out, you
take your money, and then you move on to
the next trade that you're then full
margin again. Let's look at what this
would look like in the chart. For
example, let's say you are trying to
follow a downtrend, right? What you want
to be looking for is, you know, we are
in a downtrend. You don't necessarily
need to have any specific strategy for
determining the downtrend. But as you
see new levels break below, you're going
to wait for these pullbacks. And you
want to make sure that there's a decent
reaction. You can drop the time frame if
you want to. And you want to be entering
on those reactions off those levels so
that you can then snowball that further.
Right? So after you see a reaction off
of this level supposedly off of this
level here, let's say you get in not the
perfect entry or whatever, you're going
to put sort of your stop. You can use a
loose stop too, but the reality is there
is no stop. There's no stop loss when
you're trying to snowball here because
you're either going to blow your account
completely or you're going to be making
profit. And then what you're going to do
is basically just shooting for new new
highs or lows and something along these
lines. It's going to be a general sort
of idea. you're going to full margin.
You're going to bet absolutely
everything that you can and then
hopefully it goes into your momentum
very quickly and then you get out of the
trade once you can safely. Okay, so
again, let's break this down. First,
you're going to determine a trend,
right? So, I'm going to scroll just
let's say let's say we'll just pick gold
for example here. We're going to go to
the current model in gold. Okay, this
looks like a pretty good uptrend. You're
making new highs and you know this might
be an area of resistance, but who cares,
right? What we want to do is just scalp
more profits and then we're going to get
that small account to be larger and
you're just looking for little scalps
while you're doing this and you're going
to get a few wins in a row and that's
going to blow your account up to
something larger. So all you're going to
look these large candles and then a
quick pullback. You're going to buy in
on them and then shoot for new highs.
Right? So here's here's maybe an example
back is say hey we're in this uptrend.
We see a large candle. You look for a
quick pullback off of a level. Right?
You might not have gotten in, but once
we see a reaction off that, maybe you
take that candle here. As it pulls back,
you see the reaction and then you look
for the new high, right? So, this might
have been a trade. And this is your
easiest, most probable way to win
trades. And then all you do is you just
shoot for something like 2 R sort of
thing, right? Maximum of 2 R. And you
have a really likelihood trade here. For
example, let's see again, you know, as
you're following a trend, maybe this is
a downtrend. Now, we've determined we
see, okay, there's a large candle here.
We see the pullback. We look for that
close and then you continue down, right?
So, we can say, "Hey, here's another
example, right? And then we're going to
roughly have our our account being blown
here, right? And after you see a
reaction off of these levels, right? You
see that wick?" Then you can again shoot
for a new level with 1.3 hour or so and
then close it out once you're in profit.
It's as simple as that. That's the
easiest way that you can. You're going
to do that like five 10 times in a row.
And know that's going to take multiple
times for you to do it cuz you are going
to blow it eventually. And then you will
be able to flip that $100 account to,
you know, 5 grand, 6 grand, something
like that.